Voices collide, the storm and the flame. Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive. In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
Torch light and
Psyche's show
but I can't tell you what it is yet because it won't be as pricey. But I do have some good news
though. I do have the free ebook out available. All you have to do is go here. Go here.
Just put in your name and email, and then we'll get it.
It's really good, and I think you would love it.
Let me see.
Yeah.
This is the link.
What's going on, guys?
Yeah, there's Ruby.
Here's the link
Rudy's right here you see him
Sleep in
Where's tricks? I don't see tricks around. Oh my god my hair's all
Go ahead and get the ebook it's free so
If you didn't want to check out the Drollpedia,
you're like the panel versus troll decoder.
It's pretty cool.
I want to get your feedback on it, though.
So go ahead and get that.
Let me put up my green screen.
Okay, so how is your day? How is your weekend? Do you have a good weekend? That's what I want to know um, I'm microphone on
Microphone
Where are you?
So, testing, testing, I don't know if this is the right one, I think that one's my webcam.
Testing, testing, does that sound better?
I can't see everything, it's the problem.
But, okay.
Yeah, so...
Can anyone guess what the surprises though? Guess what the surprises?
I bet you're gonna be shocked. You're gonna be like oh my gosh. This is so cool
But I can't tell you what it is yet. I don't know probably a little bit
So, anyway, let's pull some cards for the chat.
Where's everybody?
Why is everyone so quiet?
Ten people?
Everyone's silent?
Okay.
Jamie, James.
Okay, let's get reading for the chat.
Okay.
Okay, oh, okay, we got the Four of Pentacles, okay.
So this is like working on something
you've been collecting, maybe.
You've been winning over some minds, some hearts.
Maybe just collecting dates, what's going on here?
But you're, I don't know,
it's gonna be anything from a porn collection
to people you're dating, but.
I see you've hidden some stuff away in jars.
This one is called the collector.
I see this collection will pay off for you, whatever you
have collected.
I don't think it's as negative as what's on the card
necessarily.
It is upright as the collector, so I'm not going to
think it's anything too bad, but if you've been saving up
something, oh, another one popped up.
OK, so what do we got?
Ooh, we got the Five of Wands.
This is like a competition you've been doing,
but it's a healthy competition.
It's a friendly competition, maybe.
It's like, you know, this one is when monsters fight,
but they're all monsters, so it's kind of like,
they're all kind of like on equal ground.
Also, they're, these are similar strengths, so.
So it's, you know, just a little fun battle.
It could be a game.
It's not as serious as the Five of Swords,
More of a friendlier competition
Team sports maybe
Here we got nine of cups. Okay, and of cups is or this is like, you know taking time to relax and enjoy
There's a hey blue beam. How are you and of course she's taking a nice bath, but it's a
Yeah, it's I would say time for spending some time alone making yourself happy alone recharging because nine is also the
You know the permit in the major arcana. So we got this taking time for yourself to enjoy yourself, okay?
It's happiness with yourself. Hello, Joe Jacob. How are you?
Hello everyone in chat. What else do we got? Oh, we got the fool. This is like taking a leap of faith
This is a new journey starting the beginning of a new cycle the end of another cycle
You know this one says pink
Sorry, my eyes are so bad.
Take the step, take the step.
Okay, you can take a step of faith.
It's not necessarily gonna fall off the cliff, right?
But it can be a tumble.
Can you be a fall into a different world?
Okay.
New beginning for something though.
Starting over, and hearing starting over.
Maybe you're starting a project over or something.
Okay, King of Pentacles, the man who has everything.
This is a good card.
Starting over, I think maybe going towards this new wealth
or starting over maybe more materially secure
about something, okay?
I think whatever you're thinking of is gonna go really well.
If you have some kind of business in mind
or money making thing, I think it's gonna,
I think it's gonna heal a Chanel.
Oh, you got judgment.
He's your best judgment also judgment will be called on your enemies
Angels blowing the trumpet. It's like it's like a test is over put your pencils down no more. We're taking okay
Maybe you're gonna be tested for something too. Okay?
We had the ten of pinnacles wow, that's great. I think this judgment is gonna bring you to a really happy place because this is like
You know this material wealth abundance looks like there's something gonna be judged in your favor
Um, materially. I'll pull three more cards.
Two of cups. Coming together with somebody else
of, you know, you consider making it equal, or you both love each other
the same amount. Say, joining
together. It can be love or friendship,
right? But I always picture the two of cups as like, you know,
doing nice cheers over dinner. Okay? Two more.
Last one will be the words of advice, but there's second to last hierophant. Some kind of higher power involves some kind of
tradition some kind of
Hierophant says he sees through all the material world into your soul. So you may be seeing beyond the veil too, okay?
Ability to see beyond the veil seeing through something
not being fooled about something either and being able to
Really know somebody find the words of advice. Oh the four of wands
This one says reunited and reconciled the monster comes home
This is of course Frankenstein returning to dr. Frankenstein
Maybe like allow somebody back that maybe you thought was maybe a monster, but maybe they're not maybe these
Love you
Yeah rejoining a reunion, but I don't know if it will be a reconciliation, but at least you can be
civil, right? You can shake hands, be civil. Okay. That's what I got for the chat,
the little ones of personal reading. Go ahead, I'll pull you a few cards or if you
want to do a more elaborate reading, go ahead and hit the cash app, the cash
up on the bottom of the screen and I'll do a longer reading for you. You're also
welcome to come up on the panel. I'll get you on the panel.
But I do have some exciting news tonight you're gonna want to tune into the show
I might end probably at 4 30 or something, but you might want to tune back into the show at after 5
Okay, sometimes after 5 between 5 and 6 probably
There's a big surprise happening
Let's just have a chat right now
Okay
So
Hope you guys are good
I know I was on really early this morning at a good show it was probably but it was very late
You've always been scared of getting cards ready never give good luck. Well, I'm more of like an optimistic reader
And so it's like there's not really a bad reading, but it's it can be information if you're interested, you know
I'm probably a good person that before I'm you know, I'm gentle
And I believe that you know
We all have control over our future, so I don't think that even if it's a kind of negative reading, that's just basically maybe a warning, maybe some things just to be aware of, maybe some things you can change.
So yeah, but go by your intuition when you want to go to reading, but that would say, if you do, I'm a good person to get one from.
Okay, but there's a stream yard, anyone's welcome up.
Especially if you want a reading, come on up,
and I'll do a reading live for you.
Can anyone guess what the surprise is gonna be?
Oh, by the way, I'm gonna keep posting.
Oh, sure, yeah, I'm gonna keep posting this thing.
This is for the free ebook.
You just gotta give your email and first name.
and you can even use a fake first name whatever I don't care I mean it's just
like you know I'd like to you know then I'll be also you know you'll also you'll
maybe hear from you once in a while you don't mind
I won't bug you I promise
Do the link to the book and that's in here. Okay, so what do we got?
Wow, okay now I've lost
Control or something we lost control of the black browser is blocked in the screen
Click the screen icon in the address bar to allow access what it's going on you see me
My skin blocks
Allow allow I
Don't know my blocks. Hi page
Take you
Okay, you're getting warm you're warm you're getting warm page you're getting warm
You are psychic so you know might be uh-oh. Yeah, there's the fake gymnick guys months. Can you just like?
Unceremoniously kick that person's butt out of the room
dumbass
Or I will
You know just like some nasty nasty as person hello number two is prize. How are you?
Okay, but if anybody would like a reading, I'll do free readings, of course.
They'll probably do three or five parts for free.
If you'd like a longer one, you can always donate.
I'll be happy to do it.
It's up number two.
Yeah, so, but you will want to tune in after five o'clock.
I don't know, maybe I'll keep this stream on, I'm not sure.
Hopefully, I'll get some of most of it on the intake.
It's all going down today, right?
So, yeah, so I'll just put these away for now though if nobody wants to do a reading.
Okay.
I don't know. I feel like I've talked, I mean, I'm kind of getting scared, like, do I have enough to talk about, do I need more?
Like, I think, you love to come up? Oh, you can't, you can't. Okay, come up later. Okay, great.
Yeah.
Thank you, Paige, for like, you know, Paige has always been a real one.
Hello
Being gang clumsy. What's a big surprise? Yeah, you'll find out after five o'clock
Can't tell you because I would spoil it. I want to
See your faces when I won't see your face, but I would love to
See everyone's reaction when they see that I didn't get excited
I do believe so
Yeah, I wasn't gonna go on until the surprise but I was like I'll hype it up a little bit
Not like I you don't need to because it's gonna be exciting. Oh, you love the new logo. Thank you
I did like I did design a new logo. It's kind of more colorful. You can see it here
Or my
You can see like that
This Joker finally coming to visit me, okay, he could be it could be him, right?
Hello Laurie, how are you? Yeah, it's gonna be good. It's gonna be good
It's going to be exciting, it's going to be a surprise.
Do you like my rings?
Yeah, so I went to Sam & Chat last night, I don't know if you guys heard.
I was on this morning, it was a really good morning.
It was with, you know, I had summer on, I had Goddy was on, Mace and the drummer was on.
Apollo Apollo was on super cool oh gosh and it was funny though yeah that's
talking about some stuff like you know I was watching Kate the turtle she played
the beta interview and stuff like that yeah it was even Kate the turtle was
like
Wow, she's I just gotta say if I was having someone scream at me like that and then like, you know, bronze bird
Like she's she's like I would have just been a bitch, right?
so
By what if I was a bitch that's why it was it's not easy plus my microphone was like barely
I was so low anyway, but I heard back. I could barely hear myself anyway, so it's like
It was a really need to like scream over me like not her but me
This was the one that's on the trip, but Kate Turdle also said some other stuff.
I mean, Kate Turdle's not a fan of mine, right?
She...
He's like, oh, well, yeah, I'll do psyche, you know, a piece of garbage, you know, months ago
But she's like, people are just figuring this out and that. Yeah, I understand. But then she even turned around to my side a little bit about it
So, you know, she also is like, oh my gosh, Mason shouldn't be in
the panel verse
You could hardly hear you. Yeah, I know Nancy because I was like, it was just like, I don't know if you can hear me better now
if I need to be real close, but I wasn't like
That close to the mic, yeah, whatever. You know who this is? That's just like the fucking Tony person again. Oh my god
He's like the only the only troll. I mean, can you put mods, please help on top of that. It's like really sick
like
Hello tree frog. How are you?
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much, Lori. I'll do another reading for you or anybody else.
Yeah, I got my microphone up now. This is a much better microphone. I want to thank the
person that sent me this microphone. I really appreciate that. I don't know if they want
to be named for that because now I do have people threatening, people that donate to
me and stuff, so I'm just going to keep things anonymous unless you let me know. There's
Doug D. Okay, so Doug D. Oh my gosh.
wow guys I mean that's just like I don't even like to read stuff like that but if you can just
delete that it's just like really disgusting and
definitely slanderous like absolute slander
so also like this is a product of a stick mine that somebody would say something like that
You make excuses for everything.
None of it's your fault.
You want to blame others, it's disgusting.
But what are you referring to?
Give me an example, I want to hear.
I want like, you know, if you have an argument,
you go ahead, but if it's just gonna be like, you know,
bullshit, okay, okay.
I'm sure that, I'm sure if that was true,
there would be some, well, first of all,
I wouldn't be, you know, free, but I think there would be
some kind of paperwork on that, you know?
I just want to.
point out I mean the biggest docs in community ever looks for everyone's paperwork and so
That would definitely be on that, right?
so
Please stop starting slander what?
This person do it what hit this guy's known God that guy
Would you like a person to lead it completely and time out for 24? No, no hide the person you can hide the person
Like someone that says that shit. It's like that's not gonna be somebody that's gonna come back be nice tomorrow
It's just pure fucking pieces garbage. I mean, I will hide them if I need to but it's like
And when you do hide them everything will disappear all their messages will disappear. Okay, okay, I'll get them
I don't know, it's not amusing anymore.
I know I'm very lax, lax on mod sometimes.
Or telling you not to mod that hard,
but you can feel free to leave people like,
oh, thank you, thank you, Laurie.
Yeah, clumsy, just let them be hit.
People that are saying crap like that, it's disgusting.
Hey, Samantha, how are you? Oh, thank you guys already. I already have 10 legs. That's amazing
That's really good. Like I'm oh my god. That's like wow. Thank you guys
Because sometimes I've done like five hour shows and like had like less than 10 legs
I was like wow sometimes it makes me feel like
So the person have anything to say though about like what they said I never take responsibility
have I don't know I mean what but what have I really done I want to figure I
think responsibility I accidentally reshrined Vita for like two seconds I
accidentally I don't know what or what I do on purpose I made an AI song so is
there any like anything else I mean what's what else did I do that's so wrong
Oh my gosh, Antib, well, there we go, oh I love it, thank you so much, thank you so
much, Lord. Yeah, like I do have, like it's probably the same troll over and over,
it's probably just Allied, who also has like, you know, a channel that's just full of basically clips,
but then it's like, he's just like, clips from me, but then it's like, he's misrepresenting everything in the clips, like.
Making it seem like I'm like some some monster. It's kind of like and
Definitely slander fitting a picture of my front door
Video videotaping whenever I got Docs and stuff or when people doing their pizza and like laughing cuz yeah
Oh, and no, no, you didn't mess up. You didn't mess up. You're fine. You mess up
If you feel like you hit somebody that shouldn't be hid
Oh, you want to hit him? Yeah. Yeah, all you have to do is just redo it. Yeah
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. You should justice for anti-bullied a vision. Wow
Kind of ironic, huh?
But um, yeah, there's been some pretty disgusting stuff
Anyway, so is that right to have like, you know, what if your front door was on on a video or what if like, you know
Someone was like, you know docked like out sending pizzas. Oh, look here. He is like during
Alexandra's show getting a new gifts, but like sending
bags of fertilizer to my door. I mean, it's like the fertilizer is sealed. It doesn't smell. It's like
Biggest thing was that was kind of heavy, right? So I had to like and I had to like pick it up and like
Oh my god, the police are on the way. Oh my god. Look at this guy. This guy is this old loser. Thank you so much. You guys are fast
Thank you so much
Yeah, not pretty creative. It's just the same person over and over and it's like really stupid
It's just like saying like the most horrible thing
Uh-oh, Lenore
Come on
Wow
It's like you
Yeah, I know Jamie. It's kind of crazy, huh? I know and I know Jamie's not a hundred percent
I'm just like, oh god
Hey, Kate. How are you?
Yeah, I but I did I did watch Kate the other day, you know, I
Enjoyed the commentary on the on that panel. I didn't enjoy it
And I told you I did a, I did a, it's a fake Kate. Oh, shit. Oh, damn.
I think what you do is really disgusting in your work. Oh, okay. That's, okay.
Well, you're, you're, you're, uh, you're, you're impersonating someone.
That's really disgusting. First of all, to not even be on your own, you know,
you're not able to back up anything you say because you're a fake person, right?
It's like, it's just an allied master computer again.
Maybe Kate would like really like to appreciate like knowing that you're, uh,
Like you're doing
But uh, yeah, we'll be on top. I'll be on top of it too. We're having obviously a little bit of a
negative
Negative thing. So thank you. Yeah, it's high those people
But any like really anybody that's like so negative especially, you know, just uh
Yep
Thank you. Oh, thank you. Yeah, oh my gosh
Don't harass Jim Nick either. I mean, it's like sort of first thing Jim Nick you're personating. Okay, literally
She's very she's she's ill right? I think you Samantha because like why are people are you going after her?
It's like, you know, I'd rather people go after me than Jim Nick, you know, or it's like
That's just really sick
So how many pages was that, guys?
Like, A, do you think that's a real Doug B?
I remember that person used to be in the chat,
but he hasn't been in for months.
And I'm not trying to bring attention to it or anything,
or like, you know, oh, I'm mad at dealing with trolls.
It's like, I'm dealing with trolls like I want to.
It's like, this is like,
ridiculous. It's like it's just called a sock puppet and now it seems like oh my gosh like all
these people are saying but I know you guys are smart enough. Thank you. This is, I just
haven't worn it very often but yeah thank you. It's a, I think it's a kid's brand or something.
You have to be back, okay love ya. Yeah there's a lot of, there's a lot of ults. Like I don't know
you know how people do that. Like I have like you know maybe like 10.
And I don't even use them, you know, I just used to use them when I was like really easy to keep that up chat all the time
Thank you. It's a nice blue. I like this nice blue color. Yeah
You see I'm a neck I have my necklace to it. I just make it. Oh my gosh the good times updates and clips while I think this necklace
It's pretty cool
That's happened
Does anybody recognize any of that
Here we go. I like it a lot.
I need to get like a nice chain on it. Wow, good time. Yeah, it's like it's really funny because
it's like I, you know, I've always been accused of being like too nice and stuff, right?
It's okay. It's like I know it's it's going too fast. I know I always been like
Accused of like being too nice or like being like wow like too trusting to goable to like and it's like just to like
Be considered like this like I don't I don't know even if that one person and that yeah, it's like wow
So it's well some people do believe that like when I'm people say it or like, you know, they enjoy it
they're trying to I
don't know but it's like
People that think I'm like so so
Hey, babe. Hey. Hey, babe. Oh
Baby
Let me go crazy. That's why I came in
Hi
There's miss Lenore. I know I
Don't know if that's the multiple people or it's just a one guy, but yeah
This Lenore I miss Lenore a little panther
It's just like
Yeah, the reason I have alt well, it's cuz I have like I had several accounts for different reasons
You know and so then I but then when I started getting like hidden in cats. I used to like
You know going and going on an alt except now that the like a few people that I like actually wanted to do that for
Have evolved them
So it's fine like oh never mind
Yeah, Miss Lenore, you're gonna fall. Come on, babe.
There, throw my arms.
Yeah.
Hi.
Hello.
You're sweetheart, huh? You're a sweetheart.
Like this it on my shoulder come on
Like a parrot when it's like a parrot. Oh, you're drooling on me. You're drool
your drooler
Your little mouse breath. No, but I don't think Lenore is the one that likes the mice. It's actually Lola Lola loves mice
You're my little protector
Okay, you're gonna sit on my shoulder Eric, go ahead sit on my shoulder. There you go. I'm gonna sit up there. Okay
I love that she's purring real loud. You see Rudy over there? There's Rudy. Rudy
Hi, she is a sweetheart. She's a very sweet hearted cat. I love you
Okay, go down, go down, there you go.
You wanna go down?
Okay, I'll sit up there.
Yeah, healing is healing for,
I heard like, you know, when a cat sits in your lap
and purrs, it like heals all.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
Like these, thank you so much.
I think I've been pretty good at picking out
good shades for my face.
Of course, you know, I like,
I'm always looking for a good deal.
And so of course I got a good deal, no.
Oh, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm gonna eat you, I'm gonna eat you, eat your ear, get your ear, you know what I mean?
Okay, then R went to sit there like a, a shirt, shirt, shirt, you know what I mean, okay.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, Luna was very protective, huh?
Your tigger was so much aww.
Tigger aww.
She was a talker, she looked like a dog.
She sat on your shoulder and came to her name aww.
So cute.
Lenore's your favorite.
Don't touch her, it's a riddle.
Okay, I'll have that one.
Lenore, Lenore's my little.
You're my little love bug.
Hi.
You're so talkative. Hi, talkative today.
It's welcome, Arthur.
Going down, going down.
Hey, brother.
Brother was the one down there.
Thank you, I love this setup, bro.
I'm loving this setup.
You got a nice clear back.
You got the green screen going on.
You're like chilling on the chair.
You're like leaning back, leaning back.
Yeah, I have a little like, I have like a little kind of like a conductor, well, there you go. There goes that.
Looking good, brother.
Just update everything now. So yeah, looks good. It looks like you painted your wall. It's like you got a different lighting going on.
Trying my best trying to make it
Look better. Oh, actually, I have some new backgrounds to let me try a new background. You got like a button up going on
You got the fuck saved
Hey, it's price tonight, but I can't you know, you're really inspired today. Thank you
Love it. Good thing. I love
Put out my free book for my free book today. I'm loving the vibe. You know what I mean? Thank you. Yeah, I
Glad because and I yeah, I'm just really
Enjoy how the show is looking much better and I got every I got I was able to buy actually a lot of things
I needed like my computer and stuff
It's really changed because now I can watch the show on my big screen TV
You're watching yourself
Yeah, I have the volume nice all the way
I can like play it loud and like it's not like you know echoing or anything
Dude a trip cake is a
He shout out to him, man. He's the one that at this point keeps me updated with all
The drama between you and your friend. I know yeah, and I was like actually I was like
It was the day before yesterday. I was in two of his because I was like, oh my gosh
And then I was like I've been like in a lot recently. I'm like, okay. Well, I'm in the middle of all this drama
but I feel like he's very fair about it and like
He plays he plays like both sides of stories and yeah, yeah, so I think he's really really good
You know he's unbiased. I think everyone you know everyone in those videos appreciate
It's because he keeps it, you know, straight down the middle and this is what I have learned.
Like Dita has gotten mad at these trip click videos. I've heard a couple comments hers
and I said, but why would you get mad at his videos? He's literally playing everything both sides.
If you're upset that you said something and that you're upset that he's playing it,
you can't really blame him.
Right, I mean I today found a channel. It was you know Allied Master Computer channel. He has a channel
It's all just like clips of me
Like oh here. He is at the pier harassing Indian tourists here
He is at the pier harassing the guy putting up a sign. I'm like, hey, what's up? You're on YouTube. Whatever that stupid day
I was kind of drunk in the fear of yelling at her like everyone. I was like here he is, you know, like, you know
Eating like a pig or whatever here you again. It's like and then then he was posting of course picture of my front door
pictures of him like sending food to my house and like me getting like deliveries of like manure and food and stuff
And it's just like okay, but it's like but most of the stuff I was like, okay
Should I like you know do privacy complain should I do harassment and I was like, you know what it's like
They're these are just clips from my show. It's like, you know people can interpret them like they want to of course like you know
He's interpreted them in a very negative way, but I I've not ashamed of my anything. I've done
It's on my show. I put it there, you know, it's like so it's not I'm not gonna like be mad
I mean he's going too far so I can be kind of like mad. I'm not gonna go mad like far enough to like
To strike if he actually privacy struck me recently. Yeah, because well, I didn't I didn't show his picture
Just his picture, but then he has big videos of me with my full face and he's shown himself on my camera
There's double standards, bro. People have double standards. They're weird. He's trying to get me in trouble
but you know what YouTube let me know before they did anything and he like kind of like
They're like, oh, well, you know, they're like just delete it if
Or you know or delete that
Part of it and then we'll like look at it later or something and so I just delete it real quick
And so I didn't think trouble YouTube's been really really kind to me like I know I think I just got really
Lucky at your dad rescued her from a construction site in the empty
Pool she couldn't get out because the ladder steps weren't built yet. Oh my god. Oh
And just in time for Florida heat. Oh my god. Can you imagine? Oh my god
Wait, did you read something? What are you? I don't get it. I'm reading the comment. You're completely just derailed. I am so sorry
Yeah
and uh, but anyway, I don't know this has been like there's so many like
It gets I don't really get that negative about people, right? It's like even like people. I don't like I really won't
I mean I have before I've got I've gotten like, you know
My diva, but I think I've calmed down a lot, but it's like I
Mean the amount of hate I get for the amount of love I give out. It's like wow
It's like I really like try to give love out and try to be like love everybody
You know, it really do and it's like it's not easy sometimes
Do you think
And you you know what you don't even have to answer this and if you don't like the question whatever
Do you think that she?
It hasn't been the whole, in fact, pro-Israel.
You think that's what also, there's like seeds there that clash?
You think that's the issue, too?
No, I don't think so.
No, I'm very, not even political, but it's like,
you know, I'm not against any race or religion or anything.
But I don't get into politics, you know, so it's like I but yeah, so I don't think that there's I'm not speaking out about anything
So what is there to be mad about? I don't know. I just kind of stay neutral about political things
I guess you wouldn't be neutral, but then they get into like one side or the other. I just I really don't follow politics
I go, hey, Jay dog. How are you?
That's how I honestly, and this is I'm gonna just end it with this
I guess, you know, we don't want to talk about that that much, but
The Muslim religion is just so weird. I'll just say that like a very weird
You know they had
Religion can be considered weird all the they can all Jesus, you know, there's prophets in Christianity with prophets in Judaism
Prophet they're all actually Muslim is from Abraham, right?
Hey Abraham is the father of all and so they're actually brothers like the other big they're like brother religion
They all came from the other one
Christianity came out of Judaism and then Muslim came out of Christianity.
We didn't even see that talk about Jesus in the Quran.
Also, it's a beautiful language and it's a beautiful written language too.
Beautiful art and beautiful music is wonderful.
I mean, there's good aspects to religion too.
When it gets to extremism or it gets to hating other people that aren't part of the religion,
or not welcoming people into the religion.
That's where it gets kind of weird,
but I don't know, I'm not anti-religion.
I'm just anti-using it as a kind of mind control
and or using it to like in politics,
like legislating and religion, making the law,
the religious law the same as the civil law,
I think that they should be separate,
just like American founders intended, right?
Freedom of religion, but freedom from religion as well is implied right because we don't have to follow any religion
Like unlike some countries that don't have freedom
Politics were good yesterday
Well, when I when I was talking about them because yeah, we had some good discussions about
Psyops and about, you know, it was a little bit
I was just a little bit afraid because I was playing some stuff from a good
Channel that they're obviously big on another channel because they're not pretty on YouTube for a reason
I'm just kind of being a little bit careful with it. So I did private to the last night's video
We had a good discussion
I showed some crisis actors who were obviously crisis actors, not saying that the incident
wasn't 100% real, but they do follow up with crisis actors and create a narrative, right?
Or something like that.
So, there's a lot of weird stuff going on, but yeah, I enjoyed talking about politics
a little bit, but I don't like to get it.
That's because we were all able to, like...
understand each other right even if there's pro con him and it's like that
everyone was able to be pretty agreeable with each other hello yeah my bad I
went under the hotline tunnel and I completely lost connection but I was
saying like and I'll end it with this the Muslim prophet you could say like
okay every religion is based off of something okay yeah
You know, but they believe in totally different things. You know
The Muslim prophet married a 12 year old. That's yeah, but that was culturally at that time. It was like
allowed was culturally not too unusual or else it would have been like an outrage back then, right?
It's like there really was that it's like even today if you have like younger right
I don't think I don't know if they get big big or sexually active with them until a certain age
But I don't know I know I don't of course it's like you know
You can say that but it was thousands of years ago, right or over over two thousand years ago or something so
Yeah, but this is the thing though. So yes, it was thousands of years ago, but you ask a lot of these Muslims
What are their thoughts on that and they don't they don't back down from it. They're like, yeah, okay
So, okay, what what do you want me to do? Well, I mean it's like, well, you know
Are you talking about American Muslims or you're talking about Muslims and you know that area?
I mean, there's I'm sure there's I've seen interviews. I guess they're there. Maybe I guess from that area
Because they have a stronger accent
But it's like they double down on it. It's like, whoa, like that's kind of weird that you have to double down
Are presented to us like that. It's like, you know
It could be a lot of bias and I don't I don't know
But it's like, you know, and it's also people's religion they get
Like people will say oh because of that the religion is all bad or something and so it's like it's kind of like
Trying to take away. So it's like they're gonna be more
Knowing that from the past. I'll stick to Jesus Christ. I'm sorry
Again, I'm not saying that everything in the Quran is incorrect, but that one thing it just ruins everything else for me
Well, there's a lot of stuff that might ruin the religion for you
Like if you look read the Old Testament, like the God is a very angry God a very jealous God
He's always like favoring one
kind of people over the other people and saying oh kill everybody else and
Unalive their children and blah blah and it's a very scary God and then the Jesus is very
It's a very, you know
Loving kind of being okay. We oh, I'm sorry Arthur. We lost him again
Your camera's not on or something. I don't know. I can't bring you on because you're either camera or your microphone isn't working, so
But anyway, yeah, I mean I'm willing to discuss these things, but really it's like
I think there's a lot of misunderstandings and I don't know I just don't know the truth and so
I'm just going to respect people's right to do what they want.
So sometimes, oh, it's almost five.
Oh, my gosh.
So the surprise will be happening soon, guys.
Oh, shit, I need to check something real quick.
Shit, shit, shit, hold on.
I got distracted, and I was supposed to be checking something.
Yeah, Arthur. I can't bring you up because I don't see you. Your camera's not on or something
Okay, just need to check something real quick. Okay
Wow, I'm getting a lot of follows on Instagram. It's going crazy. Okay, so
Okay, so
Okay, so 30 minutes and we'll be on our way to our destination. Oh, here he is. He's back. Okay. Oh
Now he's gone again
It was just a brother. Yeah, we keep going right now. So two quick things two quick things
I do yeah my bad horrible connection
Two quick things the people in the chat you guys got to hit the thumbs up
Hit the thumbs up and if you can you guys got a dollar at the very least come on
Let's don't know the dollar man. Let's I think we should start off small
Let's do a dollar a day at least and then we can build ourselves from there
Oh, I really and I do appreciate anything anybody
and I will do longer readings. I will definitely make it worth your while. I'm not just begging for, you know.
For such a big deal I mean time is money at the end of the day time is money time is the most precious thing in this
On this earth, you know you guys can do it to really help me out, too
Is like I know I did release my free ebook and it's like it's a hundred percent free
It's just nice the site and give your email and first name
You don't have to give your real first name, you know, you should give your real email because that's the link's gonna be
but yeah there you go that is there's a link right there and you can just you
know just get up basically a really nice nice report and it's gonna in the book
is great too but so yeah that if you just do that that helps that even if
you're just here participating and a friendly I appreciate that too for
spread but yeah but any everything's appreciated I do have some very very
Donors that have kept me afloat and that have been generous and I think everybody I really don't like when I have a falling out with somebody
They're like, oh that person
They used to like you I'm like, well, I know then and I don't know they don't anymore
But it's like I never I never changed to them. It's like it's like not me going like disrespecting them or anything
It's like I
Always tried to be respectful. I know there's a misunderstanding with Christine and everything
Like where she's like
I mean, she just took it all the whole wrong way.
I was talking to Crystal, Crystal was saying ridiculous things.
I was just getting her to talk and kind of just thought she looks...
I think...
Christine, with all due respect, needs some dick.
She needs to relax.
well let's not I'm not gonna say that but you know it's like Christine I hope
like you can find your heart someday different than me I didn't I people are
still like you should apologize to Christine I'm like I apologize to
Christine I said I'm sorry I wouldn't have done I do and do again if I knew
how she felt about it but I thought that she'd have a different sense of humor
about it but yeah Christine is like a dick bro she needs some dick
And again, all these words are coming from me.
Psyche does not agree with anything.
Christine, you need a dick.
Okay, well, what do I know?
Bita said something about me.
She's like, oh, she's like, should I just say
Psyche's dick is shredded off into like a thousand pieces
because they're not having sex with people?
What is that even mean?
It's just like, she said something stupid like that.
How does she know about your personal life?
I don't know, I don't know.
You can say the same thing about her.
Right, it's like do I know anything about her sex life? No, but I'm not gonna say oh her vagina is drier than a biscuit
No, I'm not going to say that right no anyway
Or you could say how about you stitch your fucking pussy cuz ain't nobody gonna enter in there, okay?
Well, you see I'm gonna get in trouble now. It's like oh my god. He was he was talking about that was me. That was me
Well, we remember it was the whole uncle thing that started everything
She continues on that ever since ever since that happened. I think it happened in May like it's like it was like
Six or seven months. I was like absolutely fine with her no problems at all that happened and ever since then it's been downhill
It's like this machine and she always will bring that up like oh
You did this back then like okay, okay, I get it. I get it. She's idea get over it
Yeah, it's just words ain't nobody come for you in real life. We're not we're not killing you
We're not killing your cats like relax girl. Jesus. Well, the thing is it's like I never even did anything like
I mean like people have doxxed her me and you know people have you know gone
I could put against us and it's like we should have like stayed strong together and instead like
people of
She's allowed people to affect the relationship. I haven't because
I'm still here. I mean, I was always willing to
To work reconcile, but it's like a certain point. I get sick of apologizing. I don't feel like I did something wrong
Of course, I really don't think I like it did something that I don't know if it's not taking responsibility
Maybe you know, maybe I did something wrong in her. I guess in her eyes. I definitely did but
In the grand scheme of things. I'm not out there trying to harm her and there are and so it's like why aren't we worried about people trying to harm us?
actively rather than our friends
Like who just do something we don't like. I mean this is ridiculous. I'll end it with this
I think a Christine needs a dick and if she's gonna continue being a fucking Debbie downer
Go ahead and bite a bullet then Christine go cry go away
Anyways, psych you got a great channel here. You got a great setup. I'm loving this new setup. I hope you stick with this
Thank you. I am it's gonna sit me a bit. It's gonna have better and better
I mean, I'm just slowly upgrading as I can but I have more stuff in mind too. Yo, can you that green screen?
Can you put like a like a bunch of cats?
Yeah, like just a cat meme just a bunch of cats there. Have you made it? I can do it. Okay. I'll watch. Thank you, brother
Okay, see you soon
Let me see that. I can find a cat to me.
Let me see. Like, there's a lot of cats to it.
Let me see.
Let's see.
Oh, there's Grumpy Cat.
Oh, remember Grumpy Cat?
He was a cute cat.
So, you're gonna get to see the surprise
at like 5.30.
I can't tell you too much about it
because I wanted to be surprised still.
But, hold on.
Okay, well, I don't have one with a bunch of cats, but I can just have I have a cat meme
Here you go. I mean I can find one, but I just don't have time right now. So you see I'll put it up
There we go, I don't know people
It's so weird with me
Okay, add cat meme right here. Yeah
I have to take the mean part out of it,
but I'll just have to cat space up there.
Oh, there we go.
Thank you.
Cute, huh?
Okay, so at 5.20, I will leave.
I'll try to, maybe I'll start a new stream.
I don't know, or maybe I'll give myself a few minutes
to make sure everything's okay to tape and everything.
So, you guys will be surprised, you'll never guess.
What I'm gonna do, you can probably already guess that.
But it'll be fun
so
Anybody before I go. I have time for some some readings or
And if anybody let me know guys
Let me know if you tell me if you like
Opted in for the book and then tell me how you like it and like I wanted I want honest opinions and
Not it's not a difficult read. It's like a fun read
There's a lot of information about and it's like, you know, I was gonna like do let's just like kind of tell all
with these books
But I didn't
because I don't want there to be
Problems where I have to take out somebody's name later or like, you know
So I did change change the names to protect the innocent and not so innocent, right?
But I do give some examples of some stuff that's happened. You know, there's some things that we obvious
I guess somebody yesterday said oh my god. It was kiss my cheek. She said well, I talked to
Alexandra and Alexander said oh, I've read the troll book
I know exactly what you are or something like that and she's like well much like I think I deserve a free book because my name
No, her name is not in the book
Um, it's just there's types of trolls in the book and so, you know, she was identified as a type of troll book
But she was out actually on the show last night and she was real nice. And so, you know, she's not a bad person
Okay, hey shepherd. How are you?
So anybody want to talk before I go because I'm gonna be
Gone for a few minutes, and then I'm gonna restart the stream. I think
Good on battery good on data. I got everything that everything I need I can bring my cards, okay
Yeah, it's gonna be cool
So guys, just tune back in, whip it in the stream,
just tune back in in a few minutes.
Aw, she's so cute.
What a cute kitty cat.
Aw, a cute cat looking over me.
I love little gray cats, you know.
I love a white cat or a gray cat.
Well, I do have a gray cat with little of a, you know.
I like that, it's all gray too.
Okay, well, it's really quiet.
Nobody wanted a reading
Hopefully you guys are out getting the book and stuff, but I'll be back
Check back in at like 530 to 540 right and
It's gonna be a big surprise
Big surprise you guys are gonna be shot shot
It's gonna be fun
Okay, I'm gonna take you along with me. You're gonna see something cool
Okay
Play a song
Oh
from sight.
さっき
to end the show because I'm going to go to do the thing but hey I'll be back
shortly okay I will be back on very shortly so guys after 5.30 just check
in like in 10 minutes check in like 15 20 minutes and you'll get a big
surprise okay
Thank you.
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat losing air
Alex tried to joke, boom, sent into the night
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike
Diamonds feeling spicy, shirts slipping down low